Since
we're talking about the third level of the
kingdom, the form,
what are we going to do, the third, the third
level of the kingdom, the form of four
days by Hans Sachs and Nîmes, these four
have sexy names, this by Harvard in
Game, these four have
boring names, Transformer, and the first, the
level of the form is made up of the
second level,
Robert Ford, fourth, infinite space,
infinite space, internet,
canches, nes, is infinite consciousness,
blindness, nothing at all, in which the
summit,
Webber, we will get to that,
so the third level of the form,
Falcones, has five components,
F
is the main difference between
level 2 and level 3, the ball to your
insides, fin, in level 2 you are inside
the thing, in the light star party in
Maine, and there your body and mind are
in ecstasy, sol, you must, Pichincha, can,
sicken, the difference between the second and
the third, and art 5 of Part 5 of
Gateway, okay, you have to think about the
person who gets drunk, oh, I would
n't have arrived, anti-football, manches,
watching live, I know that nobody here
has  Never drunk but
others have seen him get drunk on First Air
Selena first they're going crazy in the
East Kit drinking and yes yes they keep drinking
dislike
LAN Airlines and his heartbeat /
like before
parade for common line on the plateau if
that moment feeling the sense the
mental feeling
happy goes from happy
to unconscious
and that's the difference between 2 and 3 is the
usual sharp as if you've
taken a very strong drug
sleeping lecturer or like five
sleeping pills First Bank your
heart and the first you're happy in art
fire line and after five you're like this already
the mind at last in the
mental feeling is night
whoever it is I can't I can't
describe it in
words they just have to feel it like this the
flat plateau of Bari faithful in the
body feeling this Dutchman
if being like you're doing
a good yoga pose the body very
integrated
church
the body feels super charged like
a ballet dancer so when your
balance is perfect everything is super
charged
if the whole body you have knee problems
Chester crisis thong or you went to a
very strong ashtanga class
which makes you wish you could sit
in a chair on Friday  surrender
your knees interrupt your meditation you
should sit in a chair by
Jaime nor defend meditations
Washington EFE don't make this law
the express and the exception 'breaks' I
try different postures objects to
meditate and sit and because I know
someone who sits on bricks
only to Nihat Burley Wire in the Park and
Uruguay in the body you are like this
all activated in mind the feeling the
mental feeling we'll be a man
while yesterday
[Music]
the mental feeling went
beyond mental pleasure to an
indescribable plateau in the great and tex
well art to have and maybe it takes you an
hour it will arrive and surely disconnect from
here so let's just pretend what we
must do
to sow a seed so that it will
happen in the future
in the same way we did when
trying to imagine our past life
the first couple wish the fighter Ma
Ying-Jeou the first two weeks that you
try to imagine your past life and Google
are Fanny Stories Live from Fantastic in a pretty good way
and give so that
funny stories will appear like the
movie Fantastic Four the
Fantastic Four in the live pour  and
San Miguel Roca can eat better and not
Santiago Cam and how to see you said
suddenly you connect with a
real memory something real will appear software
form so let's try to
be on the third level of the kingdom of
form and Manning of Jordi and reading the
mere fact of imagining that you are
doing it here on YouTube and that can
cause you to be there
are distant in the bar and Fidel Suárez
the body is completely activated
modified mind film institute
and the mental feeling went from a
pleasant state to
dissolution the whistle hearts and mine
the mind if you are completely
awake nor punctual focused the fear
fix and two more things work in session
in Zinc
are very strong at this point in this
part you can tell me what session who
can tell me what turns and Zinc
is theme
I am without scamming to dance that if you have
the fire alarm
Jason this Smart Fit actor is the
smoke detector
and when it detects smoke
the alarm is activated I am Jaycee immense
state vacation alarm main 7 is an
alarm in the back of your mind
and nothing
irsap basteri folketing Jaime inside  The
heart flat line
exposes that your object of meditation is
inside the heart on a plateau the x5
javier fort koffice but if you
suddenly think of our four coffees
in distracting the voice
jr firewall and peep and if suddenly
a thought of the four coffees arises your
fire alarm goes off tit it
and piti the news chamba world mba ya and at
that moment you use gemba that of solitude
behind the mind or the tension or the focus
back to that plateau my my father and
fishing my dad really liked to
fish
during the second world war he was
in a submarine san gil and they hear her and she really
liked the sea anipac
weaver
and for you that
animal and stupid
in the attack on the pines where he
offers he
bought one like a boat like 20
meters capable of firing torpedoes
at other ships of that type john f
kennedy was captain of this type of
military ship it's lay it's
like almost a suicide mission
and it took us 34 days inside the
sea once poker in face and we played
poker and fishing we go
and the two of us fish  that they fish, let's go, they were
big like a tuna,
and wait for English, you have a
special belt with a big hole right
below your important place,
the witness arrives
because I'm talking about this, about that topic,
wei, mango, about the mind, it goes
and then brings it back, you release the
reel and then you tighten it, you release it and tighten it
and it climbs,
alak, yes, if not, you don't fish them all
because that terrain
of talking,
you tighten the piece, you fish the wings,
but then you relax and let it go and then you pull it,
if you let it go, and that's how you move,
and then my dad made us open the tuna
and take out the entrails, there will be Capi and
Klein, and you start in the place, peeping, the
character, and you cut up to the
silver neck of the man and take out the guts from the
water, city news leader, and 15 years later
the doctor told him that he had a
heart problem,
we have to do surgery on him,
but don't worry and that he has the family home,
we can grab a vein from your leg
in my mouth, juniors be the place at
figure  And we're going to cut you just like they
cut the dog.
I didn't know about karma, but I thought I missed you.
Sorber survived, but it was unpleasant. It
will be the third labor, so at the
third level,
Fidel meta feeling, the mental feeling, they have, it seems they are
sleepy, they want to
do something, you
plan, since the inguat trusts
you, your mind function, sastrón, and there are
two mental functions that are already
strong, the
distraction detector alarm,
orangel Washington
maingot companies that is always
vigilant to see if the mind gets
distracted to another place, if it
leaves your meditative object,
which is the pleasure of the heartbeat,
and I say always, if it is another place,
extra
Colleen Peck brings it back, the
sporting opposes in a punctual way, of find, it is
so, you have to see and of being one way to
die, Sting
Ribéry, Cleaver of the neutral, everyone
knows what neutral is, to missionary light,
and ours made the things live
keys like tiger in the last state,
this is sugar of its own, the one that lasts,
you already drunk,
here the emotions enter us, no  They
move my car and the good guys
and not knowing IGTM online
were drinking tea
American Airlines
is talking about some people from China
who have special powers that
hit them and they become immobile and mutable
and there's not much there's not much but the
mental state is like immutable without
emotion without image vial although
beyond any feeling that
Velasco is that seeing and measuring is nothing
that there's no way make noise now each
pair in their room of this fetid toy
versus
receiving the 50 dollars there's an
extra fund to Nabai they gave this deficit now
I know who who did who to whom of
whose are to their phone with with
confession who was who's going to confess
and stickers Frank Van Hattum I hope it
was from the hotel
someone's phone rang in
meditation
if we need some cash and whoever does
n't pay their cell phone and it rings 50
dollars
here at light.com let's
go I
'm not sure if this is going to work in the afternoon
but let's try it
because we don't have much time let's
try it
Winnie Mediterranean have to meditate in
the afternoon EFE
preliminary  In the morning, if you
did the preliminaries in the morning,
interest with straight a nature, well,
directly enter your
breathing, they are the standard of time
and there will be, we are going to spend some time
focused on breathing,
Monjack, they are long installations,
Roxana soundtrack of having the same, it
is not in the boom, focus on the
outside sounds like the air conditioning and
the small sounds inside this
room
to travel,
compare that to the beat of your heart
and I talked to him,
abandon your focus on the air
conditioning
inside the entity,
pierce and enter to center your mind
penetrating inside the heartbeat
and art,
you are the heart, you become a
heart in the film, it comes once, it
feels delicious, appetizer,
there is a lot of peace and pressure,
very joyful, Paris, they take several months
after seeing and water,
your body is
electrified, mind awake and
conscious and I saw in a perfect
external posture, heart beat the hard way, time,
detune,
stay in the heart, become the
heart, be the heart, but with that
joyful feeling,
they have the joy, there is no
one else, the ex-lover of the
angels,
imagine that someone put
headphones on you
in the Saunier Duval feelings and  He also put
headphones on your
excessive feelings, avoid the feeling stop,
and all feelings stop. In
the main,
they put earplugs in your ears, he's
no longer with those feelings, and
Wendy, see, and inside your mind, entity, you
go deeper into the heart, and the
feelings are no longer there. What lies where
there's no motion, as long as it's a
place, a space in the heart where there are
no more emotions.
Steiger Farfán is protected for five
minutes. What to see,
Watson is strong. Keep your state of
alertness and attention very strong.
Bieber and Telemann Bach.
Keep your vigilant one active and ready
to bring your mind back if it gets
distracted by another object and to bring it back
to the center of the heart, to the place without
feeling.
Sound Connections 3:
The exhalation in long breaths,
since you can't open your eyes. Nacho Martín
2: My art, they throw Iguazu,
much more difficult for me after
eating. For these, it was difficult, okay, it
was eternal life. Let's
try to
practice the fourth level. Let's see
what the master teaches us. Maybe there won't be
a nap, and he won't teach us to fall
asleep.  a little nap
the men me what's the sun capital
this column there is no good nobody nor
image and someone asked me what the
ejection text is capable
very well
while taking care
is with Julian Assange this text these
meditations come from a text of
jets are layer that is called the jewel of the
essence
are his star comments I do
n't think he knows that he had something to
do with the text maybe he wrote it
strong
form we walk
fourth level of the kingdom the form and
sizes stage after stage min
stage means that there are only three
components in this fourth level
[Music]
of single my mind station and 20 hs in
the mind
remains focused nor punctually on
an object of the neutral faithful at this
end the non-neutral feeling is the
same
the ability to make your mind
refocus on its object meditate
meditative is called perfect
to perfection perfected huayhuash
observing very easy
harding you don't do it you don't fight you don't
battle
how many parts
of this verb that there is active of boxing
this is debatable this verify and
study in other books and well it
says that when you are on this
meditative platform you are no longer  generating neither good
karma nor bad karma only neutral karma
all from Birnau Tavern this year and
name and in this year in Antwerp and tenth
for the Tibetans who are studying
Tibetan and DJ also The First Bank
these plants of her and also my girl
from Tax Minsa Cam Newton
in this state you are not doing either good
karma nor bad karma neutral karma
fixed norm of Mexico normally if you are
happy you are generating good karma only
flat line and softline of fasting and quini so
the neutrality of the
meditative plateau is so neutral that you
are not generating good karma nor bad
karma I am
not convinced I am not totally
comfortable with that explanation of the author since
from Huanca mind vision I am going to continue
studying but that is what a
comment says this post Biffi and
strong jurist form the fence making
it is supposed that if you reach this fourth
level of the kingdom the way is generating
super good karma
to the check I am going to study it more
before with him
at this moment
I'm still line and off line in your
feelings at this moment are  so
neutral are so neutralized bridge
nuances starter but it's much easier
to stay there from the bikes stents me
mine you can your mind exerts less
resistance systems on the platform on
the third level if there was resistance in
the Ford EX and looted crossing
and on the fourth it's like you're already
floating
want to try it
what's the main difference between
level 3 and 4
the extension bikes you mind less
resistance your mind is wet flow is
like more influenced a flow very the govern
of the benefit of the field if you go out a
little your object is easy to get back
here and beni ready and surrender
efe have
a coffee Esteban of the same level
who wants efe
really
to the house
ok
[Laughter] I
'm not
ok beni ready
from Bogota I'm going to arm yourself that
you saw the bed and then we're going to study
half an hour more of calm because if we
have to finish the study Daniel
realized something where are the snacks
[Music]
is being sued also we have to see
and it's a matter of me already answered your
question the same the home is a matter more do
you want to know what your question was and if
Oliver without  The gray vines is the only
person who asked me this question from
Slide Juniors Phoenix of so rich I love
life viola a you never finish the
tantric wheel of life to that mind we are going to
meditate
camps be prat
with your attention the breath
I'm in to
bring your mind inwards
the 10 long breaths
long and slow installations
I
focus your mind on the realm of desire
observing the air conditioning and other
sounds and objects in the senses
and don't focus on your heart yet
focus you are in the air conditioning
before traveling
now I enter the beat I
have in the I have
entry focus on the
heartbeat
makes a comparison between the
feeling of focusing on the
heartbeat and the feeling of
focusing on the air conditioning and
decides which is tastier will be in the
heart and abandons the air conditioning
focuses on a channel of feeling and nobody
in the reader and I saw the dance classes was
born action in letting go in you are
inside the beating heart and you
focus
on a pleasant physical
bodily sensation and also on a
pleasant mental sensation
nothing
if they come to the topic in the  Videna, did you think
we're hawks, Ticia in the park, and in
the image,
the pleasurable feelings of the body
and mind do not
move, as if someone
had anesthetized you,
Philip Rivers
3,
and exhalation in long, slow breaths
in the field of meditation
[Applause]
of questions, I also had a
thought of that question of the two
Tom Hanks,
the girl
[Music] I
think in my opinion it's a
neutral physical feeling,
so this post has
six goals on YouTube, while feeling
so far is supposed to be
the physical enjoyment and neutral feeling in
Haiti that can fade away, voice of
feel like some have wanted anesthesia
before, a pressure and minimal variety of
sensation, I think the goal is that you
feel like someone who has just been
anesthetized and your body no longer has
sensations,
Isner and Gilles Lights
Nam, so you're not
physically electrified, just your body feels
numb, fasten up, but I'm not sure what I'm going to
check, okay, they write from
Carmen or that we do something from the Carmen studio
and to
The Street and Jones
30 News,
you
will follow  Studying now, well, here are
forms. Now we go to the four
formless realms, weak and Brahms forms.
Perhaps they are actually formless realms? I don't know
why you say no, from the
southern age to the year of Job, and
putting forms that are the cause to be
reborn in a formless realm, but they are not
the realms. It informs when you enter
this type of meditation. It simply
generates the causes to do so. If you were to
die at that moment, these are
layers. And Ford Fondas, more here. These are
layers in the four realms. They inform,
well, in Sun Times, The Complete, which from
Disney is Vox
Stern and pop bands from you, it's from a book
by Stanley Bando and Meet the King and
Hardware. It
means that the two categories,
Acz,
are the six, the five plates of the
senses plus consciousness. They are six,
and the six objects on which they focus,
Queretaro industrial, in Sanskrit it is
called, it is, na,
sometimes they call the four
meditations, the four meditations of the
realms. It informs, so don't get
confused because your mind never talec and
from Isaf
Game Night Names, these are good
names  These are beautiful web names, the
captive name and measurement member, the
names help you remember the
meditation of Firstbank Code
Infinite Space in the after the
first is called infinite space or endless
space without limits, sub so
competitive and right guard come to see the
jam damaging numbers city never tyson and
ambition daniel comba hp multiseat in
mind that we went from fun to
hookup powers of definition
ok here comes the definition
during the four meditations of the
kingdom the way to wiiware focusing 'we don't
concentrate on the heart at 3 am you smell
and when you concentrate on the heart
there is an awareness of the physical heart of
the ancient forms of meditation and when you
immerse yourself or enter into the
meditation of the king informs us to get to
detect ok past
grab the heart in getting to the network
break town and and soft and you're going to make
the heart you're focusing on
previously dissolve I'd like to
work so we're going to start on the
heart piringer the beating heart the
physical heart that beats to wilson and
serve and nights, that is, the awareness of as well as
a piece of meat in your
tissue in your  Chest tissue of the heart
and the transition you make from that
physical heart with molecular tissue
to one without tissue is similar to the
transition you make from air
conditioning to the heartbeat. It
refers to sitting and saying, "Now camp your
heart."
So if you teach
this meditation, you have to say, "Now
compare your physical heart, which in the aftermath,
with infinite space."
Xavi Twin 23 themes between those two steps.
Staphorst Abdallah forms in the fourth
step of the realm of form. This law
was great. If it is being in your heart, there is a
lack of forms. Really, Hans, upon
entering the meditations of the king,
informs us of the IOR jarc breakdown. The song "
House of Keeping" that you be the house of
extractor before your heart allows
your heart to dissolve like a
sandcastle you built
when the sea's waves reached it and
dissolved it.  Or that sand
turns into something more infinite, like the
way it is, and not like a sugar cube that gets
wet.
If there were seals, leave behind, focus on
your heart, the
holder of the day,
the picture of the decade, a new mind. This is
when you abandon the image or the
conception of physicality
in your mind. With your mind, it dissolves. It's
physicality in the middle of bosses of each
edition. It's already a dissolution of the
physicality of everything, and specifically
of the heart beating with
family fabric, with exteriors missing that I
lay
cool
for me. I don't know why it has always
felt like a
horizontal horizon. I don't know why the
heart dissolves like sugar.
Happy wool in Cheste.
This artist among the chosen ones in finals
at the stand, and the mind
extends towards all infinity, and if it
continues to extend like this, never to
cease. They sharpen to Blake
and it's already Sperling year after year. The goal
is
[Music]
a sensation, a feeling that
expands you. If it expands, it expands. If you
continue and continue and continue and continue and it never stops, it
never stops and continues.
The guards have, then.
In the entire expanse and totality of the
infinite universe,
we have to try. We have little time.
We are going to observe the breathing and then
we are going to dissolve the heart. Watts
Annette, to see what condition
the body is in in this meditation.
Nam, in this test, the body is
anesthetized.
Watney Motion, what emotion do you have? Nothing, nothing,
a neutral emotion. PSOE, in this
too, your emotions are
anesthetized. You feel neither good nor bad.
Vides sensational, more than partitions in
the main stage, digest
kliquers, it's phases, and you generate this
sensation of dissolution of the tissue of the
physical heart, and your mind extends in
all directions.
Nanita, by the way,
blast,
we have done five meditations, and you count
the meditation of the air conditioning, the
kingdom of desire, with fire. Look at
Jhargram, we did 550 of the kingdom of
desire,
Margaret and Sex. Now we are going to do 6
for this journey,
and just to anticipate where we are going,
we need you, don't lie, stands
when all is the dance, the Lyon.
When you do the dance, the Lyon, maximum
this value in a whole hour, but you don't, don't
stop.  Don't stop, go go,
they've moved Frank Schleck. You go from the
air-conditioned Ford
through the four levels of the realm of
form, Ford, and the four levels of the
realm of formlessness. Report the HAARP
is law.
You can go back and you do this tour through
the realm of form. You pass the king
informs us up to the fourth level and
purpose. You return from the realm informs us
to the realm of form. Natural life, that
is most airlines paint. That's
almost all of the lion dance,
but here at the end you'll have to do
something and you're going to park here in this
part of that form. There's something that's
beyond the realm of formlessness.
This video,
I'm anticipating what's coming.
Super forms of Ambo Wang, so
we're going to do a super short meditation of the
formless realm. Walter Neymar, what's it
called, in Space and Space,
infinite space without end,
although let's put in the confines
and limited
the scan straits and see directly
enter the breath
in the session. You have the sublime
and with account 10 slow installations
in Champs, identity in share, to travel
directly, enter inside the heart.
Had in leaving this artist,
Male King,
you and your heart.  And the tissue of the
physical heart begins to dissolve like
sugar when it comes into contact
with water, like sugar comes into contact with water, it
melts.
Start, stop, and state services horizon
of versions, the express,
and your mind begins to expand
horizontally in all directions
of space. Stay with that,
in the terms that are there,
and extend your mind further and further into the
entire universe. And there we will be for
five minutes. Several snow. The body is
anesthetized
in disc marter, but it returns to
breathing,
the
long exhalations that may never send good
karma and give it away. It offers it
in opinions.
You can open your eyes and get dressed.